question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Spadefish&quot; will attack you.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                                      "question": "The main playable character of the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot; is a monster.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  &quot;the Zone&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "&quot;Half-Life 2&quot; runs on the Source Engine.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
     "question": "There is a Donald Trump Board Game, which was made in 1989.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                       "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "In the 1988 film &quot;Akira&quot;, Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
